<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CountryProfile</string>
    <string name="bangladesh_text">
        The Greeks and Romans identified the region as Gangaridai,
        a powerful kingdom of the historical Indian subcontinent,
        in the 3rd century BCE. Archaeological research has unearthed several\n ancient cities in
        Bangladesh, which enjoyed international trade links for millennia.[15]\n\nThe Bengal Sultanate
        and Mughal Bengal transformed the region into a cosmopolitan Islamic imperial power between
        the 14th and 18th centuries. The region was home to many principalities that made use of
        their inland naval prowess.[16][17] It was also a notable center of the global muslin
        and silk trade. As part of British India, the region was influenced by the Bengali
        renaissance and played an important role in anti-colonial movements. The Partition
        of British India made East Bengal a part of the Dominion of Pakistan; and renamed
        it as East Pakistan. The region witnessed the Bengali Language Movement in 1952
        and the Bangladesh Liberation War in 1971.[18] After
        independence was achieved, a parliamentary republic\n\n
        was established. A presidential government was in place between
        1975 and 1990, followed by a return to parliamentary democracy. The country
        continues to face challenges in the areas of poverty, education, healthcare and corruption.
        \n\n\n
        Bangladesh is a middle power and a developing nation. Listed as one of the Next Eleven,
        its economy ranks 43rd in terms of nominal gross domestic product and 29th in terms of
        purchasing power parity. It is one of the largest textile exporters in the world. Its
        major trading partners are the European Union, the United States, China, India, Japan,
        Malaysia and Singapore. With its strategically vital location between South, East and
        Southeast Asia, Bangladesh is an important promoter of regional connectivity and
        cooperation. It is a founding member of SAARC, BIMSTEC, the Bangladesh-China-India-Myanmar
        Forum for Regional Cooperation and the Bangladesh Bhutan India Nepal Initiative.\n\n It is
        also a member of the Organisation of Islamic Cooperation, Commonwealth of Nations,\n\n the
        Developing 8 Countries, the OIC, the Indian-Ocean Rim Association, the Non Aligned Movement,
        the Group of 77 and the World Trade Organization. Bangladesh is one of the largest contributors
        to United Nations peacekeeping forces.
    </string>
    <string name="india_text">
        The Indian subcontinent was home to the urban Indus Valley Civilisation of the 3rd millennium
        BCE. In the following millennium, the oldest scriptures associated with Hinduism began to be
        composed. Social stratification, based on caste, emerged in the first millennium BCE, and
        Buddhism and Jainism arose. Early political consolidations took place under the Maurya and
        Gupta empires; the later peninsular Middle Kingdoms influenced cultures as far as southeast
        Asia. In the medieval era, Judaism, Zoroastrianism, Christianity, and Islam arrived, and
        Sikhism emerged, all adding to the region\'s diverse culture. Much of the north fell to
        the Delhi Sultanate; the south was united under the Vijayanagara Empire. The economy
        expanded in the 17th century in the Mughal Empire. In the mid-18th century, the subcontinent
        came under British East India Company rule, and in the mid-19th under British crown rule. A
        nationalist movement emerged in the late 19th century, which later, under Mahatma Gandhi,
        was noted for nonviolent resistance and led to India's independence in 1947.


        In 2017, the Indian economy was the world's sixth largest by nominal GDP[20] and third largest
        by purchasing power parity.[16] Following market-based economic reforms in 1991, India became
        one of the fastest-growing major economies and is considered a newly industrialised country.
        However, it continues to face the challenges of poverty, corruption, malnutrition, and inadequate
        public healthcare. A nuclear weapons state and regional power, it has the second largest standing
        army in the world and ranks fifth in military expenditure among nations. India is a federal republic
        governed under a parliamentary system and consists of 29 states and 7 union territories. It is a
        pluralistic, multilingual and multi-ethnic society and is also home to a diversity of wildlife
        in a variety of protected habitats.
    </string>
    <string name="nepal_text">
        Around 500 BCE, small kingdoms and confederations of clans arose in the southern regions of Nepal.
        From one of these, the Shakya polity, arose a prince who later renounced his status to lead an \n\n\n
        ascetic life, founded Buddhism, and came to be known as Gautama Buddha (traditionally dated 563–483 BCE).[36]
        By 250 BCE, the southern regions had come under the influence of the Maurya Empire of North India and later
        became a vassal state under the Gupta Empire in the 4th century CE.[36]
        There is a quite detailed description of the kingdom of Nepal in the account of the renowned Chinese Buddhist
        pilgrim monk Xuanzang, dating from about 645 CE.[37][38] Stone inscriptions in the Kathmandu Valley are
        important sources for the history of Nepal.
        \n\n\n
        The kings of the Lichhavi dynasty have been found to have ruled Nepal after the Kirat
        monarchical dynasty. The context that "Suryavansi Kshetriyas had established a new regime
        by defeating the Kirats" can be found in some genealogies and Puranas.[35] It is not clear
        yet when the Lichhavi dynasty was established in Nepal. According to the opinion of Baburam
        Acharya, the prominent historian of Nepal, Lichhavies established their independent rule by
        abolishing the Kirati state that prevailed in Nepal around 250 CE.[35] \n\n\n
        The Licchavi dynasty went into decline in the late 8th century, and was followed by a Newar
        or Thakuri era. Thakuri kings ruled over the country up to the middle of the 12th century CE;
        King Raghav Dev is said to have founded the ruling dynasty in October 869 CE.[39] King Raghav
        Dev also started the Nepal Sambat.[40]
    </string>
    <string name="bangladesh">Bangladesh</string>
</resources>
